{"data":[{"question":"It must be ________ more than that.","a":"worth","b":"cost","c":"costly","d":"expensive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be worth something: used to say how much something is worth\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"I wouldn't eat fish ________ I was extremely hungry.","a":"provided that","b":"or","c":"unless","d":"providing that","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Unless: used to say that something will happen or be true if something else does not happen or is not true.\u00a0\n- Provided that: used to say that something will only be possible if something else happens or is done [= providing].","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"When I leave school next week, I ________ this class for ten years.","a":"teach","b":"shall have taught","c":"will teach","d":"shall teach","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Future present tense\/simple present + until\/till \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"We invited them ________ the meeting next week.","a":"to attend","b":"for attending","c":"attending","d":"attend","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Invite sbd to somewhere\/do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"\"To call up\" is to ________.\u00a0","a":"criticize","b":"surrender","c":"visit","d":"telephone","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Telephone (v) : to talk to someone by telephone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"To check out of a hotel is to ________.","a":"register it","b":"leave it","c":"complain","d":"ask for a room","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Check out: to leave a hotel after paying the bill.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Children under the age of eight ________ allowed to participate this game.","a":"hasn't","b":"haven't","c":"isn't","d":"aren't","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Be + PP.\u00a0\n- Children: plural noun- are.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Employers often require that candidates have not only a degree ________.","a":"but two years experience","b":"also two years experience","c":"but also two-year experience","d":"but more two years experience","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Not only ... (but) also ...: used for emphasizing that something is true and something else is also true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Today the noise and smoke of factories ________ the environment polluted.","a":"make","b":"makes","c":"want","d":"wants","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (the noise and smoke of factories ) is plural.\u00a0\n- Make sbd\/sth + Noun\/adj: to cause something to happen, or cause a particular state or condition.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither oil nor coal ________ used to produce electricity.","a":"was","b":"are","c":"is","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Two singular subjects connected by either\/or or neither\/nor require a singular verb.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"}]}